surefit.net 2018-05-01

# Privacy Policy | Sure Fit Home Decor

Your Privacy  
At Sure Fit, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We do not sell, rent, or trade e-mail addresses. If you have any questions that are not answered below, please call us toll free at 888-796-0500 or e-mail us and we will answer your questions promptly. 

Protecting Your Privacy  

* What information do we gather and how do we use it?
* Will Sure Fit disclose the information it collects to outside parties?
* How does Sure Fit protect customer information?
* What about cookies?
* How will Sure Fit notify you of privacy policy changes?

1\. What information do we gather and how do we use it?   
If you order a product from Sure Fit, enter a contest, promotion, answer a survey, or use other features of our web site, we may request that you provide certain personal information. 

Contact Information -  
The personal information that we collect may include your contact information - your name, postal, and e-mail addresses, and telephone number. We may use your contact information for a variety of purposes, including:  

  * Fulfilling your order and notifying you of its status 
  * Mailing Sure Fit information including notices about new products, and special offers we think you'll find valuable 
  * Administering a contest or promotion that you have entered on our web site 
  * Sending you complimentary gifts for completing a customer survey on our web site 
  * Notifying you about important changes to our web site 

Placing an order online will automatically set up your account with surefit.com if you select a password during the checkout process. You may also choose not to have Sure Fit remember your information. However, having an account with us will make your checkout quicker and easier. 

If you would rather not receive our special e-mail offers and updates, please do not enter your email address on the information request page. If you are already receiving our special offers and updates and no longer wish to receive them, please click the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any e-mail update that you receive from us and you will be taken off our list. You may call us toll free at 888-796-0500 or send an e-mail and we will remove you from our lists promptly. We do not rent, sell, or trade e-mail addresses. 

Sure Fit is committed to proper Internet practices and full compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 (15 U.S.C. 7701). It is our policy to prohibit the sending of "Spam" e-mail by any of Sure Fit´s marketing partners. Please note that under the CAN-SPAM Act an advertiser is required to provide an opt-out for customers to unsubscribe from future mailings. 

If you wish, you can opt-out of certain kinds of communications while continuing to receive other materials that you desire. So if you want to opt-out of our e-mail promotions while still receiving our information through the mail, just let us know. 

You may update your contact information by calling us toll free at 888-796-0500 or sending us an e-mail. If you have a password-protected account with Sure Fit, you may update your contact information online anytime. 

Financial Information -  
If you place an order, we will collect billing information, your credit card number, CID number (3-digit security code located on the back of your credit card), and expiration date. If you wish, Sure Fit will store your credit card information for you in a password-protected account, which will allow you to checkout more easily next time you order from us. We never share your credit card number or use it for any purpose besides fulfilling your order. To read more about our security policy, click here. 

Other Personal Information -  
If you answer a survey on our site, we may ask for personal information besides your contact information, such as your preferences or interests. We analyze this information in aggregate form, looking for market trends among our customers, rather than analyzing information about any individual customer. Under no circumstances does Sure Fit request or collect sensitive personal information such as an Internet user´s medical/health conditions; racial or ethnic origin; political, religious or philosophical beliefs or affiliations; trade union membership or sex life. 

Web Site Use Data -   
We collect and aggregate data about how people use our web site so that we can provide a better experience for our visitors. When you visit us, our web server recognizes your domain name. 

Sure Fit is currently also using and has contracted with a third party vendor to track and analyze non-personally identifiable usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers to administer our website in order to constantly improve the website quality. All data collected is owned and used by Sure Fit, and is non-personally identifiable, summary information of the activities of our visitors and customers.

Will Sure Fit disclose the information you provide to outside parties?  

We do not sell, rent, or trade e-mail addresses, provided, however, that we may share your email address with our subsidiaries or affiliates. 

If you receive information through the mail, Sure Fit may occasionally share your mailing address with carefully selected partners. If you do not wish to receive information through the mail, or if you do not want Sure Fit to share your postal information with our partners, please contact us and we will put you on our do not share list. Call us toll free at 888-796-0500 or e-mail us. 

Sure Fit may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, web site traffic patterns, and similar information to our consultants and reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will not include any personally identifying information. 

In the unlikely event that Sure Fit is sold, or substantially all of its assets acquired, customer information may be one of the transferred assets. 

How does Sure Fit protect customer information?  

At Sure Fit, protecting your information is a priority. We use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving customer payment data. We also have security measures in place to protect customer data on our servers against unauthorized access. To read more about our security policy, click here. 

What about cookies?  

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies allow our web site to remember you and your preferences when you return to our site. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that and disable the cookie. 

Our cookies allow us to recognize you as a returning visitor and to retrieve items in your shopping bag and on your wish list from prior visits. We also use cookies to analyze traffic to our site and track the pages visitors view so that we can improve the content and layout of our website. The information we collect through cookies is used in aggregated form only. 

How will Sure Fit notify you of privacy policy changes?  

If our privacy policy changes, we will update this statement accordingly and provide you with the ability to opt-out of any new uses of your personal information. We encourage you to review this page periodically for the latest information on privacy practices at surefit.com. 

Links to Other Sites -  
We provide links to other sites that we think you'll enjoy. These sites operate independently of Sure Fit and have established their own privacy and security policies. We encourage you to review these policies at any site you visit. 

Children's Privacy -  
Sure Fit does not knowingly solicit or collect information from anyone under the age of eighteen (18). Sure Fit requires children under the age of 18 to consult with their parents before furnishing any data to us. 

Privacy Promise -  
If you feel that this site is not following its stated privacy policy, you may call us toll free at 1-888-787-3348, or e-mail us, or write to us at Sure Fit Inc. / Customer Service, 8000 Quarry Rd. Alburtis, PA 18011. 

Your Security  
At Sure Fit, we ensure that the information you send us remains protected, safe, and secure. We take this policy very seriously. Below we'll try to answer all your questions regarding credit cards, our safe ordering process, and Internet security in general. 

Providing for your security - 
  * Is my credit card information secure?
  * What if an unauthorized purchase occurs?
  * What does it mean when I see a "warning" window pop up during the ordering process?
  * Why do I hear so much about security on the Internet?
  * How do I know if a website is secure?
  * How do I know if I'm in a secure environment on SureFit.com?

Is my credit card information secure?  
Yes. We have taken every possible precaution to ensure the security of your transaction, including adopting industry standards for data protection. You may have noticed the Thawte logo at the bottom of our shopping bag page. Thawte is a well known Web company that validates site security. 

What if an unauthorized purchase occurs?  
Sure Fit's website provides secure transactions. In the unlikely event of credit card fraud, Sure Fit will pick up the first $50, and under the terms of your credit agreement, your credit card company will take responsibility for any additional unauthorized charges. In addition, we'll do our very best to work with your credit card company to assure that the problem is resolved with minimum hassle. We'll stay with you every step of the way. It is our responsibility to enable you to make transactions safely and with confidence. Remember, if unauthorized use of your credit or debit card occurs, it is your responsibility to notify your card provider as stated in your agreement with them. 

What does it mean when I see a "warning" window pop up during the ordering process?  
On some browsers, this window can be a bit intimidating. But receiving this message simply means that you're entering the safest, most secure area of the Sure Fit website - the order processing area. This should be reassuring since this is where credit card transactions take place. Just click to continue. Going from secure mode to unsecure mode, you'll likely receive another similar alert message, just to make sure you know what's happening. 

Why do I hear so much about security on the Internet?  
The Internet and the many ways in which it is changing our lives has been in the news for the past few years. One of the biggest concerns is Internet security because of the high increase in shopping on the web and the strong use of credit cards. Anyone wanting to take part in the growth of the web will at some point be using his or her credit card online. Keeping abreast of fraudulent behavior is always a good idea. Because of the fascination with this new medium, and the growth that is taking place, Internet security will always be a newsworthy item and an issue of public interest. 

How do I know if a website is secure? In order to be accurate, we're going to get a bit detailed here. 

When it comes to security, Sure Fit uses something called the SSL (Secure Sockets Layer), the industry standard security protocol that the Sure Fit site uses to communicate with secure browsers like FireFox and Internet Explorer. The SSL ensures that the data you send is strongly encrypted and also ensures that the site you're doing business with is the site you think it is. When communicating with a secure server like ours, these browsers encrypt the information you send in a way that is extremely difficult for anyone else to decode. (You don't have to know whether your browser supports secure transactions- if it doesn't, you won't be able to complete the checkout process.) 

Many security experts say the most important thing is what happens once the merchant receives your order. At Sure Fit, we take several steps to keep things on our end as safe as possible. We do our order processing on machines that aren't connected to the Internet, so there's no danger of people gaining access to them. Finally, we don't keep a copy of your credit card number on file. While this is a minor inconvenience - whether ordering on the Internet or by phone, you have to give us the number every time you order- we believe it's the safest and most honest way to do business. 

We are very serious about protecting you. How do I know I'm in a secure environment on surefit.com?  
The entire checkout process, from introduction to final confirmation, takes place in a secure environment. All SSL -Secure Socket Layer (industry standard protocol) capable browsers have several symbols to indicate secure mode. 

  1. The URL to the left of the colon changes from 'http' to 'https' to signify that a SSL protocol is being used to communicate with the server. (http = HyperText Transport Protocol, but https = HTTP with secure SSL.) 
  2. In most browsers you'll also see a solid blue line in the upper portion of the browser's window - another visual aid that lets you know you're browsing a secure area. 
  3. Some browsers give you a warning when you go from a secure area to a regular area. This is to ensure that people know when they've left a secure server. Unfortunately, the message can be a bit startling, making it appear that something bad has happened, when in actuality, the opposite is true.   
If you have any questions regarding security on Sure Fit's website, please contact our Web Administrator.
